Inside Tufts UP184
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Inside Tufts
1979 -- 1980
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
UP184
0.25 Linear Feet
Arrangement
This collection is organized into one series.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains a newsletter for technicians and workers who wished to unionize. These newsletters include information on the union and efforts to unionize library workers at Tufts.
Biographical / Historical
Between 1978 and 1980, a group of Tufts University clerical workers attempted to unionize with Local 925, Service Employees International Union (SEIU), in hopes of improving grievance procedures and salaries at the university. Inside Tufts was the biweekly newsletter of the movement, written by Tufts employees and published by Local 925. The newsletters include information about the union, specific issues and grievances, reasons for unionization, and efforts to unionize library workers at Tufts.
By the summer of 1979, the workers hoping to unionize had gathered enough support to vote on the issue, and an election was expected to take place that fall. Anti-union pushback from the Tufts administration ultimately led to the election's delay until fall of 1980, when the majority of clerical staff voted against making Local 925 their exclusive bargaining representative.
- Inside Tufts, 1979 -- 1980; UP184.001; 0.25 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains a newsletter for technicians and workers who wished to unionize. These newsletters include information on the union and efforts to unionize library workers at Tufts.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-04-24; UP184.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-05-08; UP184.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-05-22; UP184.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-06-05; UP184.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-06; UP184.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-07-03; UP184.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-07-17; UP184.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-07-24; UP184.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-08-09; UP184.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-08-23; UP184.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-09-20; UP184.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-09-27; UP184.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-10-12; UP184.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-11-09; UP184.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-12-03; UP184.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1979-12-20; UP184.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-01-24; UP184.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-02-07; UP184.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-02-21; UP184.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-03-13; UP184.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-03-03; UP184.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-04-24; UP184.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-05-15; UP184.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-07-12; UP184.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-07-03; UP184.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-09-10; UP184.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, 1980-09-24; UP184.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Inside Tufts, Special Editions, UP184.001.001.00028 (Box 1)